## NARENDRA HINGE

Senior Web Developer seeking roles in Application Development,Requirement Gathering,Web Development,Project Management,Software Design,Photoshop,HTML,CSS,PHP,Javascript,Corel Draw,MySQL,JQuery,Adobe After Effects,Angular,C++,Bootstrap

Current Designation: Sr. Web Developer

**Current Company: Selco Enterprises** 

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: Web / Graphic Design / Visualiser

Role: Web Designer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Highest Degree: MS/M.Sc(Science) [Computers]

Key Skills: Senior Web Developer, Web Designer, Application Development, Requirement Gathering, Web Development, Project Management, Software Design, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Corel Draw, MySQL, JQuery, Adobe After Effects, Angular, C++, Bootstrap

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

ID: 302258ec0ee9c39d56Last Active: 11-Sep-20Last Modified: 11-Sep-20

Jump to SectionWork Experience | Education | IT Skills |

## Summary

Skilled professional with 4 years of experience in Application Development, Requirement Gathering, Web Development, Project Management, Software Design, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, PHP, Javascript, Corel Draw, MySQL, JQuery, Adobe After Effects, Angular, C++, Bootstrap

Angular 6+

Work Experience

Selco Enterprises as Sr. Web Developer

Nov 2018 to Till Date

**CLIENTS & PROJECT PORTFOLIO:** 

https://painkillermedicines.com/

https://globalpharmameds.com/

https://drugstoreplanet.com/

https://www.ordercypionate.com/

https://kamagrajellyus.com/

https://buyanxietymedicines.com/

https://tramadolexport.com/

https://tramadolsale.com/

https://selcoenterprises.com/CRM/

Stepinfotech Technology as Web Designer / (PHP) Developer

Dec 2016 to Nov 2018

**CLIENTS & PROJECT PORTFOLIO:** 

http://atmamalik.org

http://atmamalikeducation.in

http://www.amiscbse.com/

http://amnda.in

Seva Sanskar Sanstha Website http://sevasanskarsanstha.org.in/ Wordpress Website

http://machitourism.com booking the Tour plan with in your budget and location. Easy for find latest events and new events booking.

aPLS Web Development as Web Designer / Developer

Jun 2016 to Dec 2016

Role:

Implementing project plans within preset budgets and deadlines

Monitoring offshore delivery management for technical deliverables of concurrent projects

Understanding client needs, requirements, and expectations and devise solutions accordingly

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad in 2014

PG: MS/M.Sc(Science) (Computers) from Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Marathwada University, Aurangabad in 2016

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

Angular 8 2020 2 Year(s)

PHP, Javascript, Jquery

CSS, CSS3, Angular JS

BOOTSTRAP, AJAX

Wordpress, Ionic 4

C, C++, Java (core java)

SQL, Oracle, MYSQL

Apache Tomcat, Xampp

wampp, USBwebserver

Adobe Photoshop, Coral Draw

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language Proficiency Read Write Speak

English

Hindi

Marathi